<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Events on Open Source Cities - Montréal</title>
    <link>https://opensourcecities.github.io/montreal/events/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Events on Open Source Cities - Montréal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://opensourcecities.github.io/montreal/events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://opensourcecities.github.io/montreal/events/meetup-october-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://opensourcecities.github.io/montreal/events/meetup-october-2019/</guid>
      <description>Let’s kickoff the new season of meetups by diving into #Hacktoberfest! If you haven’t already heard about it, head over to https://hacktoberfest.digitalocean.com/ and register to track your progress throughout the month.
Schedule: - 5:00pm Open doors, arrive early to meet the group - 6:00pm Start presentation of the day - 6:30pm Lightning talks
This month we&amp;rsquo;ll have Kim Noel talking about Open Source!
 We’ll go through a kick run down of the history behind Hacktoberfest, an intro to open source and a short demo about contributing – what a documentation contribution looks like, what a code sample contribution looks like, and maybe even checkout some core code contributions!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://opensourcecities.github.io/montreal/events/meetup-may-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://opensourcecities.github.io/montreal/events/meetup-may-2018/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s get together along with the group of people already united around https://github.com/opensourcecities/montreal to share some ideas and start interesting open source related discussions :)
This month we&amp;rsquo;ll have Vincent Cloutier sharing his experience working on ipfs.pics:
 ipfs.pics is getting reborn! ipfs.pics is an open-source photo sharing system with undeletable pictures (think of it as the anti-snapchat), that became quite large before overwhelming its creators with stars (900 stars on github), memes (russian), and porn (obviously).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://opensourcecities.github.io/montreal/events/meetup-april-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://opensourcecities.github.io/montreal/events/meetup-april-2018/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s get together along with the group of people already united around https://github.com/opensourcecities/montreal to share some ideas and start interesting open source related discussions :)
We&amp;rsquo;ll have 2 presentations to be announced soon (will update this description as soon as it&amp;rsquo;s confirmed) but the most important thing is to get there and finally meet this amazing group of people and help decide what direction do we want to take with this meetup.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>